{
    "subject": "resource/Kip_Moore",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Tifton,_Georgia",
    "human_readable": "Kip Moore was born in Tifton, Georgia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8819836974143982,
            "question": "Where was Kip Moore born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8302863240242004,
            "question": "Is Kip Moore originally from Georgia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7583096623420715,
            "question": "What year was Kip Moore born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38600146770477295,
            "question": "What state is Tifton in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34123262763023376,
            "question": "Does Kip Moore have any siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34055373072624207,
            "question": "Where did Kip Moore go to school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27972933650016785,
            "question": "Is Kip Moore married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16654586791992188,
            "question": "Has Kip Moore released any albums?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16579851508140564,
            "question": "What kind of music does Kip Moore perform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.159646138548851,
            "question": "What are some of Kip Moore's popular songs?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kip Moore was born in Tifton, Georgia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3495_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of music does Kip Moore perform?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3495_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Kip Moore released any albums?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3495_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Kip Moore married?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3495_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3495_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3495_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3495_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3495_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3495_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3495_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3495_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3495_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3495_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3495_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents explicitly state that \"Kip Moore was born in Tifton, Georgia,\" which directly supports the given query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}